let quiz   =[
    {question: "If a number is added  with zero , then the result is: _____.",
option:[
    "zero",
    "1",
    2,
    "Number itself",

],
answer:4, 
},

{
    question: "13+13+13+13= ____X ____." ,
option:[
    "7 and 6",
    "13 and 4",
    "7 and 5",
    "13 and 2",

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "What is the difference between greatest 4-digit number and smallest 4-digit number?",
option:[
    8999,
    8899,
    8990,
    8997,

],
answer:1, 
},
{question: "2720 X 52=____.",
option:[
    "141,420",
    "141430,",
    "141,440",
    "141,450,",

],
answer:3, 
},

{
    question: "What is the smallest 2-digit prime number?",
option:[
    11,
    10,
    12,
    13,

],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "What is HCF for 18 and 24?",
option:[
    5,
    6,
    18,
    4,

],
answer:2, 
},
{
    question: "What is the LCM of '6','10'and'12'?",
option:[
    10,
    12,
    60,
    20,

],
answer : 3, 
},
{
    question: "1/4 of 24 is ____." ,
option:[
    6,
    5,
    4,
    7,


],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "What is the fraction form of 0.75?",
option:[
    "75/10",
    "75/100",
    "7.5/100",
    "75/1000",

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "3/4 kg _____grams.",
option:[
    "500 g",
    "600 g",
    "650 g",
    "750 g",

],
answer:4, 
},
{
    question: "Convert 6987 m into km?",
option:[
    "68.87 km",
    "6.987 km",
    "698.7 km",
    "69.87 km",

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "Which number id divisible by 5 ?",
option:[
    34567,
    35270,
    454524,
    45270,

],
answer:2, 
},
{
    question: "Hown many kilometers make 60000 meters? ",
option:[
    6,
    600,
    60,
    "None of these",

],
answer : 3, 
},
{
    question: "The product of two numbers is 25064. If one of the number is 52, find the other.",
option:[
    472,
    452,
    482,
    480,

],
answer:3, 
},
{
    question: "Complete the sentence. _____is 8 times more as much as ?",
option:[
    32,
    33,
    30,
    40,

],
answer:1, 
}]